The key has been stolen?
（ガブリエル）
鍵が盗まれた？
Yes.
（天使Ａ）
はい
If the two keys are brought together, it will trigger an awakening.
（天使Ｂ）
もし ２つの鍵が合わされば
あれが再び…
Fear not.
（ミカエル）
ご安心を
既に捜索は命じております
I've already ordered those valiant humans to find it.
あの勇猛なる人間たちに
Hmph. So it was your beloved maiden, then?
（ラファエル）
フン… 君が寵愛(ちょうあい)する麗しの乙女か
（ウリエル）
神である我らが
人間に肩入れし過ぎるのは
As gods, I feel it is unwise for us to offer the humans excessive support.
どうかと思うね
オルレアン騎士団…
Jeanne D'Arc, of the Orléans Knights...
ジャンヌ･ダルク
Repel the demons!
（ジャンヌ）
悪魔を打ち払え！
We have the blessings of the gods!
（ジャンヌ）
神の御加護(ごかご)は我らにあり！
Release the Golems!
（ラヴァレイ）
ゴーレムを出せ！
Bahamut...
バハムートが…
I'm waiting for sunrises again
Rise up, rise up, rise up
Let me see the sun
Rage of Bahamut
People always say
"black or white," but the world is so gray
Even angels and demons were once the son of God I praise
temee no gen'in wa temee no naka kara
You're the catalyst for your own demise
zenbu hikurumete omae no saga
It's inherent to your being
kizuku koro ni wa mou you're in a coffin
But by the time you realize, you're in a coffin
It's too late if you want to do something
What the hell is wrong with me?
I can't remember what I wanted to be
Tick, tack, which is what I found
I can see the keys are scattered around
kono yoru ga aketemo nanika kawaru wake ja nee sa
Even though a new day dawns, nothing's gonna change
Yes, I know; yes, I know that I...
I'm the only one
who can save myself
I've never forgotten
All I wanna be is me
Wh-Wh-Wh...
（ファバロ）
ふっ むむ… はぐっ…
What the hell is this?!
なんだ こりゃあ！
Is this a dream? Am I dreaming?
夢か？　夢なのか？
Yeah, it's a dream.
そう 夢だ
This has to be a dream!
そうだ 夢に決まってる
I just love dreams!
夢は いいねえ～
現実の斜め上をいって
They're so awesome and crazy...
and full of surprises!
おいらを驚かせる
I'm not dreaming!
夢じゃねえ！
This won't hurt one bit!
こんなもの 痛くねえ～！
痛っ！
き… 切れねえ
I can't cut it off.
Y-You're that girl from yesterday!
お… お前 昨日の！
You made a promise.
（アーミラ）
君 約束した
Huh?
You said if I kissed you, you would tell me about a shortcut to Helheim.
（アーミラ）
口づけすれば
ヘルヘイムへの近道を
教えてくれるって
Huh?!
I cast a spell then.
（アーミラ）
そのとき 魔法をかけた
A contract spell.
契約の魔法
That's what this is?!
これかあ！
I'll lift the spell once you tell me.
教えてくれたら 魔法を解く
Huh?! O-Oh, uh...
Say, it's pretty stuffy in here, dontcha think?
そういや この部屋
やけに あっちいな
ちょっと外の空気
吸ってくっかなあ…
I think I'll just grab some fresh air outside.
（ファバロ）
ヤバい！
Crap! Crap, crap, crap!
ヤバい ヤバい ヤバい ヤバい！
I am so screwed! Like, seriously screwed!
この状況 どう考えても
クチャクチャ…
いやいや メチャクチャ ヤベえ
Calm down! Calm down! Get a hold of yourself!
落ち着け 落ち着け…
とにかく 落ち着け 俺！
I gotta do something about this tail first.
まずはだな この尻尾を…
Up there!
（酒場の女Ａ）こっちよ！
（ファバロ）あ？
There's a demon upstairs!
（酒場の女Ｂ）
ここの２階に悪魔がいるのよ！
All right, all right.
（カイザル）
分かったから
It looks like a human with a big head!
Kaisar?! This is not the right time!
（ファバロ）
カイザル！
この面倒なときに…
It's in human form?
くう…
I definitely just broke something!
どっか折れた！　ぜってえ折れた！
くう…
どこへ行く？　早く近道を教えろ
Where are you going? Tell me the shortcut, now.
I can't tell ya just like that!
Why not?
どうして？
Don't tell me you're...
もしかして…
う… うそじゃねえって！
I ain't lyin'!
Look at my eyes! Do these
look like the eyes of a liar?!
俺の目を見ろ！
これが うそをついている目か？
Over there! That's him!
（酒場の女Ｂ）
いたわ！　あいつよ！
Crap!
（ファバロ）
やっべ…
Just come with me!
とにかく 一緒に来い！
Hurry up and get on!
早く こいつに乗れ！
どこだ？　悪魔は どこだ！
Where?! Where's the demon?!
いった～い！
That hurts!
Quit pushing!
押さないでよ！
The hell you doin'?! Sit on it right!
（ファバロ）
おま… 何やってんだ
ちゃんと座れ！
Favaro!
ファバロ！
Have you stooped to kidnapping young ladies now?!
貴様 レディーをさらうまでに
落ちぶれたか！
Quit shoving, I said!
だから 押さないでって！
Hurry! He's getting away!
（酒場の女たち）
早く！　逃げちゃう！
んん…
あんた なにボヤッと見てんのよ
What are you gawking at?!
騎士なんでしょ？
You're a knight, aren't you?!
I need to break this curse and get rid of this tail.
（ファバロ）
何とかして
尻尾の呪いを解かねえと…
Should I just kill her right here and now?
殺すか？　こいつを
ここで？
No, not yet.
いや 今じゃねえ
Gotta wait for the perfect opportunity.
チャンスを狙うんだ
（アーミラ）
早く教えて ヘルヘイム
Now tell me the shortcut to Helheim.
Oh, uh...
（ファバロ）
あ～ いや…
I got it! I'll take you to Helheim myself!
そうだ ヘルヘイムへは
俺が連れてってやるよ
You will?
（アーミラ）
君が？
（ファバロ）
口で説明するより
そのほうが確実だ
It'd be better than trying to explain it all.
Y'know?
だろ？
（カイザル）
まさか…
ファバロが悪魔だったとは
I had no idea Favaro was actually a demon.
I can't believe he had me fooled all this time!
私は今まで ずっと
だまされてきたというのか…
The Orléans Knights!
オルレアン騎士団！
Why are they here? They serve the Capital!
王都直属の部隊が なぜ この町に？
我々は
We've come to this land by order of Saint Jeanne D'Arc.
聖女ジャンヌ･ダルクの命により
この地に赴いた
そこの騎士に尋ねる
I ask you, knight.
人の姿をした悪魔を見なかったか？
Have you seen a demon in human guise?
（カイザル）
言えません…
I cannot say.
What?
なに？
（カイザル）
ヤツを捕らえるのは私の使命
It is my mission to catch it.
I must fulfill it, even at the risk of life and limb.
命を賭してでも
果たさねばなりません
But if you so desire, I will deliver the demon to you without fail!
ですが お望みとあらば その悪魔
必ずや あなた方のもとへ
送り届けてみせます
I swear on my pride as a knight—
騎士の誇りにかけ…
Knave!
（ゴラン）
貴様！　その腕輪…
You wear the wristband of a bounty hunter!
賞金稼ぎの腕輪ではないか！
確かに 今は
Indeed, I do now.
But I was a rightful member of the distinguished and noble Lidfard—
ですが 元は由緒正しき
リドファルド家の正当な…
"Pride as a knight"?!
（ゴラン）
何が騎士の誇りだ！　下賤(げせん)の分際で
Don't make me laugh, plebe!
（男Ａ）
何が誇り高き騎士だ！
Some "proud knight" you are!
You're a damn disgrace!
（男Ｂ）
この面汚しめ！
これも ヤツのせいだ
This is his fault, too.
It's all his fault!
全て ヤツの…
The desire for something can make a person strong.
何かを望む心は人を強くする
Never forget that.
それを忘れるな
（ゴラン）
フン
Yes...
（カイザル）
そうだ…
私は何としても
家を再興せねばならない
I must do whatever it takes to reestablish my house.
I will catch him.
あの男を この手で…
必ず
I swear it!
Livian
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Aren't we going to Helheim?
ヘルヘイムには行かないの？
Take it easy. It's gonna be a long, expensive trip.
そう慌てんな
長旅には金がかかる
まずは資金の調達だ
We need to get us some money.
Yikes. Talk about poor taste.
（ファバロ）
うわあ… 趣味わる
Oh! Looks like we're in business!
おっと…
早速 ビンビンきやがったぜ
2,000 Rupies...
2,000ルピ…
こいつか？
Is this you? Are you a ram? Or a goat?
羊か？　ヤギか？
I'm guessing you're a ram.
羊か…
おわっ！
I meant goat!
ヤギか～！
んなあ… にゃろう
Damn.
気いつけろ
こいつ 見かけによらず強えぞ…
Careful! He's stronger than he looks!
（ファバロ）
き… 昨日のは夢なんかじゃねえ
Y-Yesterday wasn't a dream.
She's an actual, honest-to-God demon!
こいつ… マジもんの悪魔だ！
Let's get going.
（アーミラ）
さあ 早く行こう
Y-Yeah...
（ファバロ）
決めたぜ　この悪魔女を殺(や)るのは…
Well, that settles it.
Trying to kill this demon girl...
might not be such a good idea.
やめとこう
（バッカス）
ほらよ 報酬だ
Here ya go. Your reward.
You took down a real big one this time.
今回は大物をしとめたな
Yeah, I guess...
（ファバロ）
んん？　うん ま… まあな
U-Um...
（ハンサ）
あ… あのう～
Could you stop staring at me like that?
Oh, don't even think about eating it.
そんな目で ボクを
見つめないでくれませんくわ？
（バッカス）
ダメだよ～
おいしそう…
You look tasty.
Hey, quit it. That duck is Hansa.
（ファバロ）
おい よせ！
そのアヒルはハンサだ
It's this drunkard of a god's pet.
酔いどれ神様の
ペットだよ
（バッカス）
酔いどれって こら
Don't call me that!
Eat it and you're dead meat!
（ファバロ）
食ったらバチが当たんぞ
You have some nerve!
（ハンサ）し… 失礼な
（バッカス）答えろ！
H-How rude! I'm neither a duck nor a pet!
You wretch!
（ハンサ）
ボクは アヒルでも
ペットでもありません！
I'm a god! The incarnation of a god!
神です！　神の化身です！
Hey, Bomber.
（バッカス）
おい ボンバー君
（ファバロ）
んじゃ またな バッカス
See ya later, Bacchus.
Yeah.
Let's go.
（ファバロ）ほら 行くぞ
（バッカス）行っちゃうんだ
The door.
（バッカス）
おい！　ドア閉めてけ
Hey! Shut the damn door!
ドアだ ドア！
That girl ol' Bomber Head has with him...
それにしても
ボンバーヘッドのヤツ…
妙な女を連れてやがる
She's a real strange one.
Your clothes reek!
We're fixing that before we eat.
（アーミラ）
君は羊臭いね
You smell like that ram.
All thanks to you!
（ファバロ）
おめえのせいなんだよ！
にゃは～
（アーミラ）
それ 何？
What's that?
Huh? Oh, it's just some booze.
あ？　ただの酒だ
て… おい！
Hey!
Tastes good.
おいしい…
Wait, is this the first time you've ever had a drink?
おい
もしかして 酒飲むの初めてか？
（アーミラ）
ふひ～
We gotta getcha some more, then!
だったら もっと飲まなきゃな！
お～い！
酒 じゃんじゃん持ってこ～い！
Hey! Bring on the booze!
ぷはっ
ヒック…
Nothing beats the local brew!
この町の酒は格別にうまいぞ！
What's that?!
あれは何？
Dancing.
ダンスさ
この町の踊りは格別に楽しいぞ
Nothing beats the local dance!
（アーミラ）
アハハ！
Drinking is great!
（アーミラ）
お酒 おいしい！
Dancing is so fun!
踊り 楽しい！
ハア…
水 気持ちいい…
The water feels nice.
Hey.
（ファバロ）
おい 見てみな
Take a look.
All those pretty stars...
星が きれいだぜ
You're right. They're beautiful.
ホントだ
きれい…
だろ？
Aren't they, though?
（ファバロ）
チャンスだ…
This is my chance!
If I kill her now,
ここで
こいつを殺っちまえば
I can break this curse for sure!
呪いも解けるに違いねえ
Huh? This thing busted or somethin'?
んだ？　壊れちまったのか？
What's wrong?
（アーミラ）どうしたの？
（ファバロ）あ？　ああ…
Oh, uh... It's nothing!
（ファバロ）
いや 何でもねえ
そ… そういや 俺たち
まだ お互い 名乗ってなかったよな
C-Come to think of it, we haven't introduced ourselves yet!
I'm Favaro. Favaro Leone.
俺はファバロ
ファバロ･レオーネだ
How about you?
君は？
Amira.
アーミラ
Amira, huh? That's a pretty nice name!
アーミラか
いい名前じゃねえか
ちなみに
俺のおふくろの名前は ブーニャン
My old lady's name is Bunyan, incidentally.
Bunyan?
ブーニャン？
So, why do you wanna go to Helheim anyway, Amira?
で… アーミラは何だって
ヘルヘイムに行きたがる？
That place is nothing but a frozen wasteland, y'know.
あそこは凍(い)てつく氷しかない
とてつもな～く恐ろしい場所だぜ？
Ack! Did she see through my lie?
（ファバロ）
あれ？　うそが バレた？
Helheim is where I'll find my mother.
ヘルヘイムに行けば…
お母さんに会える
Your mother?
お母さん？
これと同じもの
お母さんも持ってる
My mother has a pendant just like this.
Whenever I hold it, I can faintly recall the gentle look on her face.
このペンダントを握ると
ちょっとだけ思い出せる
お母さんの優しい顔…
My teacher told me that I'll meet her
someday as long as I keep this with me.
先生も言ってた
これを持っていれば
いつか必ず会えるって
So I want to go to Helheim and see my mother!
だから 私 ヘルヘイムに行って
お母さんに会いたい
ん？　先生？
Teacher?
（ファバロ）うおおお！
（カイザル）ファバロ～！
Favaro!
Whoa! H-Hold on!
（ファバロ）
うわっ！
ちょちょ… ちょっと待て！
You vile kidnapper!
（カイザル）
この人さらいの外道めが！
You concealed the fact that you're a demon!
しかも
悪魔であることを隠していたとは…
Huh?! You got it all wrong!
はあ？
なに勘違いしてんだ お前！
Silence!
問答無用！
騎士の誇りにかけ…
I swear on my pride as a knight that I will make you pay!
貴様を！
（ファバロ）うう…
（アーミラ）ダメ！
No!
（ファバロ）
うらあ！
（カイザル）
うぐっ…
（ファバロ）
行くぞ！
Let's go!
何という美しさ…
Such... beauty...
These look good, too.
これも うまそうだ
Knights from the Capital?
ありゃ王都の騎士団か？
I ask you all!
皆に尋ねる！
Has anyone seen a one-winged demon?!
片羽の悪魔を見た者はいるか？
A girl!
女だ！
Let's keep moving.
先に進もう
We'll split into two groups here.
ここからは 二手に分かれるぞ
Understood!
The rest of you, follow me!
残りの者は私に続け！
We must retrieve the God Key!
盗まれた“神の鍵”を奪還するのだ
Demon? God Key?
悪魔…
神の鍵？
Excuse me!
（ファバロ）あの～
（ゴラン）ん？
About this demon you're looking for...
（ファバロ）
その悪魔のことなんですが…
Do you have a mother?
君は お母さんいる？
いたぞ！
Over there! That's her!
ヤツだ！
フ～ン
A one-winged demon...
片羽の悪魔…
There's no doubt about it.
間違いない
She's the one who stole the God Key!
神の鍵を盗んだのは こいつだ！
Enchantment formation!
法術陣 展開！
You're finished, vile demon.
終わりだな 悪魔め
Oh, just look at 'em go!
（ファバロ）
お～お～ やってる やってる
Once those handy-dandy knights kill that demon girl for me,
王都の騎士団様が
悪魔女を殺してくれりゃあ
呪いの尻尾とも おさらばってな
I can say goodbye to this cursed tail.
I want to go to Helheim and see my mother!
（アーミラ）
私 ヘルヘイムに行って
お母さんに会いたい
Yeah, right. She's a lousy demon.
なに言ってんだよ
悪魔のくせに！
Not that way!
そっちじゃねえぞ？
Hey!
おい！
This way!
こっちだって
（馬のいななき）
Hey!
お～い！
あっ… なぜだ？
Why...
Why aren't our enchantments working?!
なぜ 法術が効かない！
That tingles.
（アーミラ）
ビリビリするう…
Hey! Try harder!
おい！　もっと力を強めろ！
We can't try any harder!
（騎士）
無理です！　これ以上は…
Stop!
（ファバロ）止まれ～！
（ゴラン）ん？
Stop, you crazy thing!
（馬のいななき）
（ファバロ）止めてくれ～！
いってえ…
I'm in one hell of a pinch now.
ヤベえとこに来ちまったぜ
早(はえ)えとこ ずらからねえと…
I'd better skedaddle before—
Y-You're still alive?
お… お前 無事だったの？
It tingled!
ビリビリしてた！
Tingled?
（ゴラン）
ええい 片羽の悪魔を探せ！
絶対に逃がすな！
Don't let the one-winged demon get away! Find her!
Let's get out of here!
（ファバロ）
と… とにかく ここから逃げんぞ
Seriously?
マジか…
You have some nerve trying to
conspire against us, bounty hunter.
よくも たばかってくれたな
賞金稼ぎ
覚悟しろ
Say your prayers.
ハッ！　何のことだか さっぱり…
I don't have the slightest idea what you're talkin' about!
覚えてねえな
（ファバロ）
おっと 動くなよ
Unless you wanna say bye-bye to what
you're after, I wouldn't move if I were you.
お前らの大事な探しもんが
一瞬でパアだぜ？
You filthy liar!
このうそつきめが
うそつき？
Liar?
Amira.
（ファバロ）アーミラ
（アーミラ）ん？
Whaddaya say? You up for another dip?
どうだ？　もう１回
水浴びしてみたくねえか？
Yeah!
Just what I wanted to hear!
（ファバロ）
そうこなくっちゃな！
（ゴラン）
うぐっ… 貴様！
You cur!
Wait! Don't kill them!
待て！　殺すな！
（ファバロ）
ハア… ハア…
Why...
なんでだ？
Why did I go and save her?
なんで助けちまったんだ 俺…
If I'd ignored her, the curse would be broken by now,
ほっとけば 今頃 呪いが解けて
and I'd be rid of this horrid tail.
この いまいましい尻尾も…
Tell me.
（アーミラ）
ねえ
君は うそつきなの？
Are you a liar?
I-I ain't a liar!
う… うそつきじゃねえ！
Believe me! Look at my eyes!
俺を信じろ！　この目を見ろ！
My destiny,
sotto oshiete hoshii
won't you tell me?
aenai
But you're gone
ima wa tooi place to be
in a place so far away
hitoribocchi todokanai
Alone and never-reaching
oshietekureta the truth is free
That's what you told me, and now the truth is free
I miss you
I revere you
You're my everything
I will follow you
subete wa ano toki
It all began then
You're my destiny
tsuretette
So take me
yakusoku no basho e
to the promised land
See ya, Hammer Head.
（バッカス）
じゃあな ハンマーヘッド
Lady Amira...
（カイザル）
アーミラ嬢…
I will rescue you. I swear it.
あなたは… 必ず私が助けてみせる
（ケルベロス）
もう この町には いないみたい
Seems like she's not in this town anymore!
Woof, let's hurry after her...
（オス犬）
早く追いかけるワン
...and catch and kill her, woof!
（メス犬）
捕まえて殺すワン
There's no need for such haste. She'll turn up soon enough.
（パズズ）
焦ることはねえ じきに見つかる
（アザゼル）
重要なのは あの女が
What matters most...
is to whom she intends to give the God Key and where.
神の鍵を
どこで誰に渡そうとしているかだ
Favaro!
Kaisar...
What! You're hurting my ears.
On the next Rage of Bahamut: Genesis,
"Fog of Nebelville"
Illustration: Tsunekun